(Sheldon:)This has nothing to do with religion.
(Sheldon:)This has to do with the fact
that you're a tiny man...
(Sheldon:)...who still lives with his mother.
- Sheldon, you are really being unreasonable.
- Am I?
(Sheldon:)Here. Eat this cheese without farting,
and you can sleep with my sister.
MISSY:
Oh, really?
(Sheldon:)Oops.
(Missy:)Shelly, can I speak to you for a minute?
Alone.
(Sheldon:)Why does everyone
suddenly wanna talk to me alone?
(Sheldon:)Usually nobody wants
to be alone with me.
(Leonard:)We all make mistakes. Let's move on.
(Missy:)Okay.
I'm not even gonna ask
why you're pimping me out for cheese...
(Missy:)...but since when do you care at all
about who I sleep with?
(Sheldon:)Truthfully,
I've never given it any thought...
(Sheldon:)...but it has been pointed out to me
that you carry DNA of great potential.